(Sheldon:)Hey, would you like
to hear some songs
(Sheldon:)I've rewritten to get children
interested in the hard sciences?
(Howard:)Sure.
Really?
(Howard:)Yeah. Well, I like
music, I like science,
(Howard:)I like making fun
of Sheldon. Hit it.
♪ There was a scientist
who had a theory ♪
♪ And James Clerk Maxwell
was his name-o ♪
♪ J-A-M-E-S ♪
♪ C-L-E-R-K ♪
♪ Space M-A-X-W-E-L-L ♪
♪ And James Clerk Maxwell
was his name-o ♪
♪ There was a scientist
who had a theory ♪
♪ And James Clerk Maxwell
was his name-o ♪
♪ A-M-E-S ♪
(Leonard:)Uh, okay, okay.
Uh, we-we get it.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps you'd prefer this one.
(clears throat)
♪ The itsy bitsy spider
is not an insect at all ♪
♪ Because it has
eight legs ♪
♪ And two body parts ♪
(Leonard:)That's pretty cool, Sheldon.
Thank you.
Do either of you know Beyoncé?
(Sheldon:)I'd love her to get behind it.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Hey.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
Hello.
(Raj:)You guys know the new
Discovery class missions